{
  "43": {
    "answer_false1": "Light Cruiser",
    "answer_false2": "Aircraft Carrier",
    "answer_false3": "Battlecruiser",
    "answer_right": "Heavy Cruiser",
    "id": 43,
    "question": "\"CA\" is an abbreviation for what ship type?",
    "type": 1,
    "wrong_time": 30
  },
  "44": {
    "answer_false1": "Fire Control",
    "answer_false2": "Damage Avoidance",
    "answer_false3": "First Aid",
    "answer_right": "Damage Control",
    "id": 44,
    "question": "Which of the following refers to emergency measures and actions taken to prevent or limit damage to a ship?",
    "type": 1,
    "wrong_time": 30
  },
  "45": {
    "answer_false1": "203mm",
    "answer_false2": "152mm",
    "answer_false3": "105mm",
    "answer_right": "305mm",
    "id": 45,
    "question": "What is the largest caliber of naval gun equipped on a submarine?",
    "type": 1,
    "wrong_time": 30
  },
  "46": {
    "answer_false1": "Electronic",
    "answer_false2": "Aerosol",
    "answer_false3": "Mechanical",
    "answer_right": "Thermodynamic",
    "id": 46,
    "question": "What is the propulsion power classification of the Type 93 Pure Oxygen Torpedo?",
    "type": 1,
    "wrong_time": 30
  },
  "47": {
    "answer_false1": "Ship Bell",
    "answer_false2": "Voice Tube",
    "answer_false3": "Shortwave Radio",
    "answer_right": "Engine Order Telegraph",
    "id": 47,
    "question": "What is the name of the equipment that relays information between the bridge and the engine room?",
    "type": 1,
    "wrong_time": 30
  },
  "48": {
    "answer_false1": "1919",
    "answer_false2": "1924",
    "answer_false3": "1920",
    "answer_right": "1922",
    "id": 48,
    "question": "When was the first carrier built as a pure aircraft carrier completed?",
    "type": 1,
    "wrong_time": 30
  },
  "49": {
    "answer_false1": "Mine Effect",
    "answer_false2": "Bouncing Shell",
    "answer_false3": "Anti-Bulge Shell",
    "answer_right": "Diving Shell",
    "id": 49,
    "question": "Which of the following refers to the phenomenon in which a shell enters and travels to strike its target's torpedo belt beneath the waterline?",
    "type": 1,
    "wrong_time": 30
  },
  "50": {
    "answer_false1": "40000",
    "answer_false2": "No Limit",
    "answer_false3": "80000",
    "answer_right": "102000",
    "id": 50,
    "question": "What is the maximum limit of Snacks the Dormitory can hold?",
    "type": 2,
    "wrong_time": 30
  },
  "51": {
    "answer_false1": "Submarines",
    "answer_false2": "Repair Ships",
    "answer_false3": "Main Fleet Ships",
    "answer_right": "Destroyers",
    "id": 51,
    "question": "Which of the following ship types will receive one of three special buff effects upon reaching Max Limit Break?",
    "type": 2,
    "wrong_time": 30
  },
  "52": {
    "answer_false1": "Heavy Armor",
    "answer_false2": "Light Armor",
    "answer_false3": "Sirens",
    "answer_right": "Medium Armor",
    "id": 52,
    "question": "Which type of armor type do SAP guns deal the most damage to?",
    "type": 2,
    "wrong_time": 30
  },
  "53": {
    "answer_false1": "35",
    "answer_false2": "42",
    "answer_false3": "39",
    "answer_right": "37",
    "id": 53,
    "question": "What is the maximum number of Missions that can be accepted each week in Operation Siren?",
    "type": 2,
    "wrong_time": 30
  },
  "54": {
    "answer_false1": "Increased AoE",
    "answer_false2": "Increased DMG",
    "answer_false3": "Improved bullet-clearing",
    "answer_right": "Cooldown Reduction",
    "id": 54,
    "question": "Leveling up Augment Modules' Slash Attack will NOT grant which of the following effects?",
    "type": 2,
    "wrong_time": 30
  },
  "55": {
    "answer_false1": "200",
    "answer_false2": "100",
    "answer_false3": "700",
    "answer_right": "1400",
    "id": 55,
    "question": "What is the maximum limit of Coordinate Data that can be held in Dossier Analysis?",
    "type": 2,
    "wrong_time": 30
  },
  "56": {
    "answer_false1": "Obtain a 3-star rating",
    "answer_false2": "Reduce the Threat Level to Safe",
    "answer_false3": "Defeat all enemies on the map",
    "answer_right": "Reach 100% Clear Progress",
    "id": 56,
    "question": "Which condition unlocks the Oil Cost Limit feature in Main Campaign stages?",
    "type": 2,
    "wrong_time": 30
  },
  "all": [
    43,
    44,
    45,
    46,
    47,
    48,
    49,
    50,
    51,
    52,
    53,
    54,
    55,
    56
  ]
}